J. VIGNESH

ASPIRING FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT
+91-875-430-8760
vignesh470@gmail.com
github.com/Vignesh470
Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India
SKILLS
HTML
CSS
Bootstrap (Framework)
EDUCATION B. Pharm
Mohamed Sathak AJ College of Pharmacy, Chennai.
HSC
Sri Ramakrishna Misson Vidyalaya Boys Hr. Sec. School, Chengalpattu.
2009-2011
2009-2011 LANGUAGES
LANGUAGES
LANGUAGES Tamil

PROFILE

Pharmaceutical packaging Executive with 5+ years experience looking to transition to Web designing and development. Have just learned Web designing and Front-end web development tools via online course and still progressing. Eager to put my knowledge into practice and share my passion with work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Executive - Packaging

Ocean Healthcare Pvt Ltd, Chennai

Mar.2023-Present

- Exposure to Rapidpack mach 1 turbo, Strip packing machine and its operation procedure & change parts handling.
- Worked with Pharmaceutical barcode system 1D and 2D
- · Rubber and polymer stereo ordering and management of the same
- Monthly calibration of weighing balance.
- Preparation of weekly and monthly packing plan and weekly shift plan.
- Experience in handling Change control and follow up
- · Making packing of finished products

Executive - Packaging

Medopharm Pvt. Ltd, Chennai

Jul.2022-Feb.2023

- Preparation of weekly and monthly packing plan and weekly shift plan.
- Worked with Pharmaceutical barcode system 1D and 2D
- Collection and reporting of data for various types of rejection blisters to monitor material consumption and reducing the same.
- Deployment of man power to dedicated machines and allotment of contract labors in secondary packing lines

Junior Executive - Packaging

Apex Laboratories Pvt. Ltd, Chennai

Nov.2016-Feb.2019, Aug.2020-Jul.2022

- · Worked experience with both primary and secondary packaging.
- Operation and cleaning of Thermal inkjet printer and Imaje inkjet printer.
- Preparation of weekly and monthly packing plan and weekly shift plan.
- Batch packing records(BPR) and Standard Operating Procedure(SOP) preparation and requesting.
- Maintaining SOP training records for working persons of my concerned section.

Personal Goal Pursuit

Preparation for TNPSC group exams

Mar.2019-Jul.2020